

8681815336

- 🏠 Thiruverkadu, Chennai 77

SKILLS

HTML5, Bootstrap & CSS3
Wordpress
Laravel
Website optimize (html, Wp)
Web speed & responsive (html, wp)
Tailwind Css
Animated web Design
Multiple browser issues & UI
Logo Design
Contact form jquery validation

TOOLS

Photoshop

Illustrator

Figma - Basics

ARUN VIJAY

CREATIVE SENIOR WEB DESIGNER

ABOUT ME

A software professional with 4.7 years of experience as a Web Designer. My current role involves working as an individual contributor in the modules of the project and I have been a key player in the team. Interested in obtaining a suitable position in a company that utilizes my technical skills which enhances the company's-goals.

PROJECTS LIST

www.fidomarkets.com, www.littledraw.ae, www.bodysculpt.com, www.sitecarepro.com, www.prospecllc.com, www.www.moscorporate.com, www.anandlab.com, www.hyjiya.com, www.qsm.org, www.dayelevator.com, www.jeevan.org, www.scarfymh.org, etc

WORK EXPERIENCES

2018 - 2022 Sanjeevi Technologies - Web Designer

Experience in client communication and working with clients on requirements and delivery

2022 -Present Fido Acadamey - Web Designer

Experience in client communication and working with clients on requirements and delivery

EDUCATION

2014 - 2018 Bachelor of Technology (IT)

Panimalar Engineering College, Anna University, Chennai

2012 - 2014 Higher Secondary

XII from State Board - Government high school X from State Board - Government high school